

EDUCATION

Engineer's degree, Computer Web/Software Engineering

Collegium Witelona State University in Legnica Sep 2018 - May 2022

Website

https://huszan.github.io/personal-website/

Phone number

+48 606 332 061

E-mail

mateuszjacenty1@gmail.com

Adress

Łasicka 22/1, Bolesławiec 59-700

Mateusz Jacenty

Frontend developer

ABOUT ME

I am a graduate of "Computer web/software engineering" at "Cellegium Witelona" in Legnica. My goal is to find a job that allows me to gain professional experience and further improve my skills as a developer. I am a conflict-free, efficient, independent and flexible worker.

LANGUAGES

| Polish

| English



EXPERIENCE

Digis

Front-end developer (Angular), Intership 28.01.2023 - now,

| IT-Network

Networking, student intership, 01.07.2019 - 04.08.2019, 01.07.2020 - 04.08.2020, 01.06.2021 - 06.07.2021

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS/SASS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Angular
- Angular Material
- PrimeNG
- Tailwind

- RxJs
- Git
- Node.js
- MySQL
- Sqlite
- Unit testing (jasmine)
- Design patterns
- C#
- Unity

PROJECTS

Personal Website (Angular) LINK

My personal website was created using Angular for front-end, node.js (express) for back-end and MySQL as database. Personal Website allows user to access details about me, find my social media and git accounts and check out my latest projects. It also has the option to send me contact mail.

Manga dot (Angular) LINK

Manga dot was created using Angular for front-end, node.js (express) for back-end and MySQL as database. Manga dot allows you to browse and read comics/manga scrapped from the internet. User is also able to fill scrapping form to test and add new manga to website backend database at realtime.

Particle and Pralax effect (html/css/js) LINK LINK

This sites were created using plain html/css/js. On them, I've given my take on particle effect and parallax effect. I have also played around with custom music player.